playthefungames.com 2014-12-22

# 

**Playthefungames, INC., AND AFFILIATED ENTITIES**

This Privacy Policy covers Playthefungames, Inc., Playthefungames is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how Playthefungames collects and utilizes both personal and non-personal information when you use our products, services and websites.

**WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Playthefungames collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you, and provide effective customer support. We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

Personal information specifically identifies an individual and may include: name; email address; credit card information; mailing address; and phone number.

Playthefungames does not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Playthefungames uses your personal information to:

Deliver to you and bill you for Playthefungames products and services, and communicate with you concerning your account and customer service issues;

Verify access rights to premium content or other access-restricted services and software;

Ask you to participate in surveys;

Offer you product upgrades, content, services and games;

Auto-update downloaded products; and

Provide you with news, updates, targeted advertising, promotions, and special offers.

**WHAT NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

We collect non-personal information that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are examples of non-personal information that we collect:

Information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, mobile device, Internet Protocol (IP) address;

Language preference;

Gender;

Anonymous information regarding customer activities on our websites, which is aggregated and considered non-personal information for purposes of this Privacy Policy.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Improve our software and services by providing content recommendations, language and location customization, targeted advertising and/or personalized help and instructions;

Determine if you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products, and provide information concerning compatibility and interoperability;

Track content use for the purpose of paying royalties and license fees to third party providers;

Better understand how our products are used.  
THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING – GENERAL  
We allow third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites or interact with our products or services. These companies use non-personal information about your visits in order to provide advertisements of interest to you.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

**HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?**

Playthefungames is committed to protecting your personal information. We use the following controls to protect your personal information:

Use of secure connections using SSL to safeguard information when transmitted from your Web browser to RealNetworks;

Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information;

Use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as credit card numbers and user names;

Limited employee access to databases containing personal information and confidentiality requirements imposed upon employees who do; and

Subcontractors bound by contractual, technical and organizational measures.

**PRIVACY ON SOCIAL NETWORKING SITES**

When you use a Playthefungames product or game through a Social Networking Site such as Facebook (“SNS”), you allow Playthefungames to access certain personal and non-personal information that you provided to such SNS such as your user ID, first and last name, profile picture, and usage data for that product or game. By accessing a Playthefungames product or game through an SNS, you are authorizing Playthefungames to collect, store and use all information that you agreed the SNS could provide to Playthefungames through the SNS. Playthefungames’ collection, storage and use of your information is governed by this Privacy Policy.

**WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?**

Playthefungames does not use your personal information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. In some cases, access to certain products and services may require the provision of personal information to a third party. In such cases, this will be stated during the registration process, in the terms of use, through the distribution process, or in a similar manner. The third party’s use of such information is governed by that party’s privacy policy. Please visit the privacy policy of the third party to make sure you understand how they use the personal information you provide to them. If you do not wish for such a transfer to take place, you should not register for the applicable product or service. Additionally, Playthefungames may be required to provide specific access and usage information to certain content providers and rights holders as a condition of content licensing and royalties.

Playthefungames may disclose relevant information about our customers to our contractors in order for them to provide specific services for Playthefungames. Playthefungames contractors are bound to keep all personal information they process confidential.

Playthefungames may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law; (b) comply with the order of a competent judicial authority in any jurisdiction; (c) comply with legal process served on Playthefungames; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of Playthefungames; or (e) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Playthefungamess products or the public at large.

This Privacy Policy does not govern other sites that are linked to one of Playthefungames’ websites, products, or services.

**E-MAIL FROM Playthefungames**

Separate Playthefungames products, services and lines of business may send separate newsletters and marketing emails to you. You may opt out of receiving Playthefungames marketing messages. If you create an online account with Playthefungames, you can change your account setting to select whether you wish to receive marketing messages. However, we may continue to send you e-mail about products or services you have previously purchased or to inform you about critical technical service issues relating to a Playthefungames product or service.

**USE OF COOKIES**

We use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, and similar technologies to provide you with a tailored experience.

For more information on our use of cookies, please see our cookie policy

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with Playthefungames products, services and Web pages.

**TRANSFER OF DATA TO OTHER COUNTRIES**

Playthefungames processes information about our users on servers located in a number of countries. We may also subcontract processing or share your information to third parties located in countries other than your home country. Information collected by Playthefungames in the United States may, for example, be transferred to and processed in a country outside of the United States. Information collected within the European Economic Area and Switzerland may, for example, be transferred to, and processed in a country outside of the European Economic Area and Switzerland. You expressly consent to the foregoing.

**NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE**

Playthefungames does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply. Playthefungames shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States

**CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY**
